malindoair.com 2019-12-05

# Privacy Policy

### Malindo Air privacy policy

* * *

**Introduction** This privacy policy sets out how Malindo Airways Sdn Bhd (“Malindo Air”) uses and protects any information that you give Malindo Air when you use this website.

Malindo Air is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

This Privacy Statement explains the general terms on how we protect the privacy of your Personal Data under the Personal Data Protection Act 2010 ("PDPA").

 **Collection Personal Data** In order to process your booking, we collect personal details from you. These details may include (where applicable) passenger names, addresses, passport or Government issued National ID card numbers, telephone numbers, e-mail and IP addresses, credit/debit card or other payment details. In some instances we may also collect information regarding medical conditions (only for passengers who have special medical requirements) which may affect the chosen flight arrangements.

We may collect additional information in connection with your participation in any promotions or competitions offered by us and information you provide when giving us feedback.

 **Processing Personal Data** We will use your information to provide and personalize our service. We will also use your contact details to communicate with you. We may use your information to send you offer and news about Malindo Air products and services or those of other carefully selected companies which we think may be of interest to you. We may contact you by post, email, telephone (including SMS) or fax for these purposes. Your confirmation e-mails (which may include details of flight bookings or other services booked through our websites) may include marketing material which we may feel will be of interest to you from other third parties.

Your data may be used for the following purposes: accounting, billing and audit, credit or other payment card verification and screening, immigration and customs control, safety, security, health, administrative and legal purposes, statistical and marketing analysis, systems testing, maintenance and development, customer surveys, customer relations and to help us in any future dealings with you, for example by identifying your requirements and preferences.

We like to receive feedback from our customers to help us improve our service. We may contact you by post, e-mail, telephone or fax to ask your opinions.

Please note there may be instances where it may be necessary for us to communicate with you for administrative or operational reasons relating, for example, to advise you of alterations to flights.

We may also use and analyse the information that we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business.

We also collect your information when you make or send job application via our official website at [www.malindoair.com/privacy](mailto:privacy@com.malindoair.com)

 **Disclosure of Personal Data**

  * Other Malindo Air affiliates and subsidiaries where necessary to facilitate your travel;
  * Credit card verification providers, data warehouse and other third parties in order to process your commercial transactions;
  * Legal bodies as permitted or required by law such as in compliance with a warrant or subpoena issued by a court of competent jurisdiction; and/or
  * Customs, immigration or other regulatory authorities applicable to you.

**Security**

Malindo Air has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect your information from unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our employees and data processors, who have access to and are associated with the processing of personal information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your information.

 **Cookies** Malindo Air also collects information by using technologies and methodologies that enable tracking, such as "cookies." Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer when you visit our Site and are stored on your computer by your web browser. These technologies allow us to recognize your computer so that we can pre-fill data forms for you when you go to purchase tickets or display advertising that may be of interest to you. Cookies can only be read by the domain that placed them on your computer.

As described in more detail below, you can change your browser settings to refuse to accept cookies. However, if you change your browser settings to refuse to accept cookies, we cannot tailor the Site to meet your needs to the same degree, and the Site will not automatically display information during your next visit.

 **Site Tracking** We use tracking software to monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the websites. This software does not enable us to capture any personal passenger information.

 **Links to third party websites** We may link this website and/or our applications to other companies or organizations websites (collectively, “third party sites”). This Privacy Notice does not apply to such third party sites as those sites are outside our control. If you access third party sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect your personal information. Please ensure that you are satisfied with the Privacy Policies of these third party sites before you submit any personal information. We try, as far as we can, to ensure that all third party linked sites have equivalent measures for protection of your personal information, but we cannot be held responsible legally or otherwise for the activities, privacy policies or levels of privacy compliance of these third party sites.

 **Withdrawing Consent** Malindo Air values and appreciates the importance of your privacy. We take the protection of your personal data seriously.If you wish to withdraw your consent for receiving promotional materials you may opt-out of receiving these communications by sending a request to privacy@com.malindoair.com

 **Retention** Malindo Air will retain your Personal Data for as long as it is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which it was collected, or as required by relevant laws.

 **Notification of Changes** Malindo Air may change, amend and/or vary this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

 **Contact Us** For any queries, concerns or complaints in relation to our handling of your Personal Data or Malindo's Personal Data Protection policies, please contact us at [customer_care@malindoair.com](mailto:customer_care@malindoair.com)

**You can only book Maximum 7 Passengers(excluding infant) per Booking** , If you want to Book More than 7 Passengers, Please click the below button

Click here for Group Booking
